{
    "id": "847dd3035bb4445996e0018875ad5e63",
    "title": "Rewrite correctly",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "dca2fe502d4f4ffcbb0904857a365f25",
            "title": "Gap Fills",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The new version is superior .................................. the old one.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "to",
                        "from"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is taller .................................. the other boys.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "then",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My job is to supervise people who are junior ................................. me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "with",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is ......................................... most unique distinction.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "the"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is ....................................... good to be true.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My camera is .............................. than yours.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more good",
                        "more better",
                        "better"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The master subjected the servant to the ................................... treatment.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "unkindest",
                        "most unkindest",
                        "most unkind"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Ram is one of ....................... students in the class.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "best",
                        "the best"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mr. Raman is ................................. member of the club.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "eldest",
                        "oldest",
                        "the oldest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Only two posts are senior ................................ mine.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The matter had been discussed prior ............................ my arrival.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "than",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}